Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/lindseyfarrar-23a80175 (LinkedIn) www.hbinsurance.com (Company)

Top Skills

Customer Relationship Management (CRM)

Customer Retention

Sales

Lindsey Farrar

Business Development and Marketing, CRM, RWCS, WCP Greater Burlington Area

Summary

Licensed Workers Compensation Adjuster Licensed in Vermont, New York and New Hampshire and RWCS (Registered Workers Compensation Specialist). CRM (certified risk manager). WCP (Workers compensation specialist). Was named IAIP's Risk Management Professional of the year at the Region 1 conference in Princeton, NJ in 2017. Named IAIP Risk Management Professional of the year Region 1 in 2021 and went onto Orlando, FL for the International Conference.

Experience

G.W. Savage Corporation
Business Development and Marketing
November 2022 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Vermont, United States

Hickok & Boardman Insurance Group Risk Management Advisor November 2013 - November 2022 (9 years 1 month) Burlington, Vermont

Education

University of Vermont
Business Management · (2005 - 2007)